You're the only beat that's left.
You're
the only beat that's left.
I don't see the rain on me.
I'm going to walk away.
The same thing I can see.
I'm just a mirror.
I'm not gonna walk away.
I love the world.
I love
the world.
If you want to run away, you'll be
able to catch up with the next day.
Come on, come on, come on, You'll
see everything in your eyes.
I'll show you in a dark heart.
Brand new world, start me up.
But he was CP9,
and the agents they have now are the
strongest the world has ever seen.
Even among them, Rob Lucci was the best.
These pirates are too powerful!
He won!
Luffy won!
Luffy, you had his words.
You finally beat him. Way to go!
Luffy!
Everybody head to the escape ship!
We're getting out of here!
He did it!
Way to go, Straw Hat!
Your corons keep it down!
Everyone can hear us! Who cares?
We want him to know!
Hey, those voices,
whose are they? Unknown!
They're coming in from somewhere
through a transponder snail, sir!
All right, big bro!
What?
That voice!
Stop it! Huh?
They still think we're dead, remember?
You're gonna blow it! It's them.
They made it.
Aren't those the pirates we shot
down on the shore by the front gate?
It sounds like it, but sir, we saw them.
They all fell over the cliff, sir.
They couldn't have survived.
Big bro!
Oh, my God.
Stop pushing, you idiot!
We're gonna fall!
The rope's gonna break!
You morons!
Galley-La robes never break! Calm down!
Geez, I told you to keep it quiet!
We're all okay!
Everybody made it! That
was close! The Giants!
They took all the cannon
fire for us! Get up!
Gosh, they're a stubborn bunch, huh?
Uh-huh!
But hey, at least they're alive! Yeah!
Sodom and Gomorrah are okay, too!
That's great!
Look, it's not safe here.
Those battleships will be coming back.
We need to get moving now.
Right, listen up!
We got our escape plan all figured out.
Go!
Don't worry about us!
Let's all leave this place alive!
See you again soon!
Time to head out!
Move it!
You guys climb up first!
Hurry up, Blood. Rushing to head.
Getting dizzy.
All right, climb!
Come on, everybody, get moving!
I'm gonna fall! Get off!
Stop shoving!
You dummies!
I wasn't worried about you at all!
They made it, they're alive!
I'm so happy those idiots are okay!
Agreed. Good for them.
What a relief, huh?
But if you die here, it won't matter.
Yeah, you're right.
Sir, should we hurry
over to the main gate?
No, later.
First things first.
What's wrong? Move it.
We've got a duty to carry out.
Sir!
Bring it on!
I'll take all of you out!
I got trapped!
Onigiri!
Convenient!
All right.
Snow Ball.
Our target is Straw Hat.
He's on the first column.
Right. Understood, sir. But he's... Hmm?
He doesn't seem to be moving!
Straw Hat Luffy is...
Sir, he...
He appears to be severely wounded!
What?
Luffy!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and get the hell over here!
If we don't escape, we're all gonna die!
What's wrong with you damn it?
We're almost there!
Use your powers to slingshot
yourself over here!
I'll carry you the rest of the way!
We're surrounded by Snow
battleships on all sides!
If we stay here, we're gonna be killed!
It seems the pirates planned to
escape using the stolen escort ship.
Luffy!
I can't.
My body won't. What?
My body won't move.
It won't move?
Come on, don't be stupid!
You just beat Luchi, didn't you?
And we already saved Robin!
The only thing left to do is run!
Try harder!
You can do it!
Usum!
Let's take the ship to Luffy's!
We'll grab him and get out of here!
Everyone move! Get on board!
Fire!
No!
That's our escape ship!
Those bastards!
Now it's hopeless!
We're completely surrounded!
That ship was our only way out of here!
What are we gonna do?
Kokoro, Chimney, Kenpo, Chopper!
No.
What now?
We've made it!
Out of the way!
Thank goodness!
Sanji!
What the heck happened?
And where have you been?
Sorry.
There was something I had to take care of.
Damn, this is bad.
We're pretty screwed right now.
I never thought they'd attack us
as long as we still had Robin here.
I was sure the bridge and
the ship would be safe.
That's far enough.
Surrender!
Release the old lady and
the little gorilla arm.
There's no time for any of that.
Kermit, can't!
Fire.
Why does this always happen to us?
Go to them in the second kettlebell. Fire!
It was close!
Keep moving!
Fire!
Oh,
yeah.
Run!
Damn it!
They took out the bridge!
We're stuck on this column!
These bastards have got us cornered!
There's nothing else we can do!
We're surrounded!
Then this is where we'll make our stand!
Let's fight!
Don't be stupid!
They'll just keep sending more
and more of those captains at us!
All ships, prepare to open
fire at the first column!
All the Ganons take aim!
Eliminate Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy!
He's in trouble.
You've got to do something. Crap.
This is bad. No way!
No good at this distance.
All I can do is grab him
and throw him into the sea.
Bad news, you guys.
Straw Hat may have won the fight, but
now he's so weak, he can't get up.
He'll be killed.
Straw Hat! No! Straw Hat!
I don't give up!
Stand up, throw head!
Come on, stand up!
Pirate guy, run! Yeah!
Luffy!
Hurry, move it!
Damn it, you've got to do
something right now, Luffy!
Luffy!
Throw head!
Come on, you can do it!
They don't give up!
No, I'm in trouble.
There it is again. What?
Hey, you're trying to kill yourself?
Stop spacing out.
Now's not the time.
Whose voice is this, anyway?
That's right.
It's the same voice that I heard before.
What's going on over here?
What?
Those voices? It's my guys.
No, that's not what
I'm talking about here.
I've heard it for a while.
No!
What?
Look below.
It's coming from...
over here. Below?
Who's that?
What the hell? That voice.
It says look below. Who does?
What are you talking about?
All ships open fire on the
first column in Stride, Luffy.
Commencing at five.
No, Luppy!
Jump in the sea!
Four!
The sea!
What's up?
Robin, can you still
throw Luppy into the sea?
Leave it to me.
Are you trying to kill us?
Jump in the sea won't help a damn thing.
We're gonna be safe!
She came to rescue us!
Jump! It'll be okay!
We still got one more friend here! Two!
Chopper! Did you see?
Yes!
Now, see and float.
One!
Delphinium!
I'm moving!
Is Robin doing this?
To the sea!
Jump!
Follow Luffy!
Go!
To the sea!
All of the pirates are
jumping into the sea! Ha!
There's no way those idiots
will survive in these waters!
They're done for!
Those Straw Hats are
completely out of their minds!
Let's go back, everyone!
Back to the seas of adventure.
Everyone, get on board the Mary!
Mary!
I came to get you!
What are they thinking?
If they jump in the ocean,
they're just going to drown!
And they have Devil Fruit
users with them as well!
It's suicide!
Hold on, look at that!
Is that their ship?
It's gotta be! See?
It even has a Straw Hat's fire flag on it!
How the hell did it stick
past all our battleships?!
I don't know who you are,
pal, but I sure owe you one.
This is weird.
What's going on, Sanji?
Something wrong?
Not wrong, just strange.
The rope ladder got dropped down, but
it doesn't look like anyone's here.
What?
Yay!
Yeah!
Seriously, can't you swim
on your own, brother?
Alrighty, up you go!
Hope you enjoyed the ride!
Robin! Yoo-hoo!
Leap into my arms, darling!
Over here!
We're on the ferry!
We're back on the ferry!
I love you, Barry!
I love you so much! Thank you!
Mary!
My sweet Mary is still alive!
I don't understand!
Why did she make it here?
I wish I could give you a
hug, Mary, but I can't move!
This doesn't make sense.
I saw the ship drop into the ocean myself.
The question is, who sailed it here?
We'll figure it out later.
Just get us out of here.
Great.
Let me think.
Everyone ready?
Sanji, get up!
What are you doing?
Whatever you want me to do, Nami Sweet!
That was a close one.
I thought those battleships were
going to blow me up for sure.
Hey, Robin, you saved me. Thanks a...
From now on, leave everything to us!
Luffy, everyone, thank you.
Sure. Sure.
Don't worry about it.
That's nice, but save the sappy stuff!
Till after we escape, okay?
You take that back, you heartless bastard!
Yeah, you bastard!
If we sit around, we're just gonna
end up dead and stupid I don't care!
Apologize to Robin! That's enough!
Both of you, stop!
Hey, wait, Chopper, you're moving again.
Huh?
Now that you mention
it, I guess I am moving.
I was afraid I'd never get better.
Now apologize to Robin already!
Give up yet? No! Never!
Okay, let's go!
You guys ready to move? Yeah!
Put it together, you idiots!
Are you just gonna stand
there and let them get away?
If they're gonna escape anyway, we
might as well blow up Nico Rabbit, too!
But...
but we're supposed to
capture her alive, sir.
Tragic, I know, but that's
what Aokiji said to do.
Now, all ships, prepare to fire!
Uh, Admiral Aokiji said that?
All right, man, take aim!
All ships, prepare to fire!
Revenge, prepare to fire!
Okay, so I lied, but that's
better than letting them get away.
I'll make them pay for what they've done.
Can't you load those
cannonballs any faster?
Do you want them to get high?
Spawn them still alive, huh? That sucks.
They're gonna fire!
Catch the wind from
starboard and head east!
We can't, we're completely surrounded.
All those big scary cannons and
they're aiming straight at us!
In this range with that many ships,
there's no way they're gonna miss.
Fire!
Help!
Wait, are they firing at each other?
There ain't can't be that bad.
What was that?
Where the hell are you waiting?
Something's wrong.
It's like the cannons just
did that on their own.
Don't make such stupid excuses.
Change cars!
It's too late!
They're coming straight at us!
We're gonna crash!
This is madness!
What the hell is going on here?
Look over there, sir!
The Gates of Justice are
closing for some reason!
The gate can't block the current anymore!
With these whirlpools around, we
won't be able to control the rudder!
So that's why our aim was so bad!
Don't get sucked in!
This thing keeps going from back to work!
Put out the fire! Quick!
We're gonna have to jump ship!
We're finished!
Those damn fools!
Why did they close the gate?
Hurry the hell up and open it again!
We can't, sir!
The operation lever is on
the bridge of hesitation!
It wasn't our fault!
That turned out better than I thought!
Sanji, is that what you
did while you were gone?
Mm-hmm.
I figured it'd take more than just
guts to get out of here alive.
Bingo.
You'll like my hero forever, Sanji!
Are you a genius or what?
It's a little early to be kissing his ass.
These whirlpools are
a problem for us, too.
Oh, great!
Thanks a lot, Sanji!
Would you shut up?
It's not a problem.
As long as we're together, there's no
sea that the Going Merry can't cross.
Right!
You're so cool, Nami! That's right!
Go for it, Navigator!
Just hold them off while
I find a path for us!
No problem!
One-sword-style, 36-caliber-6!
Dammit!
Why do you idiots keep missing?
It's right there!
We've got less a million cannons
firing at that stupid thing!
It's just one little ship!
They're coming your way, Luson!
I got him here! No way! I
missed one! Sanji, help!
Pause, coot!
Ah, guys, save some for me!
I want to fight him too!
Really?
Are you gonna squirm him to death?
Hate to break it to you, Captain,
but I think this one is our battle.
Take a nap.
We've done it.
You won't take a nap.
I'm gonna make these guys go me.
Just gotta get there.
I'll give a medal to
anyone who can hit them!
One shot is all attacks!
All ships concentrate attacks
on their back deck! Fire!
Shut up, Zoro!
You can't tell me what to do!
You're ready?
Let's go.
Uh-oh, I think they're coming back!
You never let us down, huh, Captain?
I guess we needed you after all.
You people are monsters!
Uh-huh.
I've got it.
The path to victory.
Chopper, helm hard to port!
Nine o 'clock!
All right, you got it!
They're pulling towards the waterfall!
What should we do?
Just shoot them!
What the hell did you do?
How hard can it be?
Save that damn ship!
They're riding the
current of the whirlpool.
It's no use.
We can't keep up. All right.
I get to be useful, too.
You can do it, reindeer dude. Yeah.
Let's go.
Full speed ahead.
Damn it.
Those bastards.
I had the power of Vinny's lobby.
The power of CP9.
I even had the power of a bastard call.
They practically burned
the whole island down.
And yet, even after all that,
even after all I've done,
I can't take a single woman away
from a tiny band of riffraff!
It's not fair!
Chief Spandam!
Please, someone help me!
Clutch!
Oh, jeez, Douglas, are you okay?
Yeah! Go!
Well, I guess that settles that.
All right, Franky, it's time
to do your thing! You got it!
Get ready, kids, because
this is going to be wild.
Bluff their hats!
Don't let them get out of the portal!
Just so you know, this might
bang up your ship a bit.
Sorry about that.
Kaido!
Wait, what?
The pirate ship is flying?
How are we supposed to top that?
Our cannons can't reach that high.
If you think that Mary's an
ordinary ship, then you're wrong.
She's flown through the air once
and she can do it again no problem.
Special Attack Super Fox Star!
It's a smokescreen!
Put them pirates! Go!
Don't let them get away!
We can't, sir!
It's taking all we've
got just to stay afloat!
We gotta get out of this whirlpool first!
Maintain fire!
Don't stop!
Looks like the straw
hats are safe and sound.
Good.
Now let's get the hell out of here.
Let's go, Puppin' Tom!
We're heading home!
I didn't realize you were here, sir.
We haven't given up the chase yet.
I swear it won't end like this.
We must maintain our dignity as the Navy.
No, as the World Government.
We'll bring down the
Straw Heads at any cost.
Nico Robin is in the palm of our hand.
We can't let her escape
again after all we've done.
Admiral,
allow us to call in reinforcements and
we'll overtake them as quickly as possible.
Don't bother. But, sir,
the force that we command
with a Buster Call
is as powerful as an
entire nation's military.
And yet, look at the state of our fleet.
Look at Annie's lobby
burning to the ground.
The situation is obvious, isn't it?
The day is lost, men.
We've been utterly defeated.
You sure you want to sit up
on top of that cheap head?
Of course I do.
That's the captain's seat.
Well, there you go.
Careful not to fall.
Sure.
Thanks for the help, Monster Granny.
You're the best.
And thank you, Mary.
We never would have made
it if you weren't there.
I was pretty surprised when you showed up.
But when I think about it, you've
always been there to protect us.
We've always counted on you.
Anyway, I'm just happy you've
been part of the team, Mary.
You're a good friend to have.
I don't mean to spoil the mood.
Damn, you guys did some
crazy stuff back there.
I don't think the
government's gonna let you
off that easy after you burned
down their flag. Whatever.
It doesn't feel like a big deal to me.
The only reason I did
any of that was because
they took our friend and I wanted her back
We couldn't have done what
we did without your help.
So thanks a lot
Well, like you said it wasn't
really that big a deal.
I just do what I had to do
Point is we're all together coming
back in one piece and this fight was
Thank you.